我们，是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文！
and Steven!
史蒂文的梦
翻译
presisco
校对
BBBB
特效
CCCC
压制
DDDD
史蒂文？
Steven?
史蒂文！
Steven!
你还好吗，伙计？
You okay, bud?
你看电影时睡着了
You fell asleep during the movie.
我本想让你接着睡的，你睡着时可爱极了，
I was gonna let you sleep, you looked so cute,
但接着你哭了起来，这就不那么可爱了
but then you started crying, and that was less cute.
不，我很好
No, I'm fine.
我不知道为什么我开始哭了
I don't know why I was crying.
我的梦并不算悲伤
My dream wasn't really sad...
哦，天，看看几点的...还有我的土豪金新表！
Oh, gee, look at the time... and my classy new watch!
让我送你回家吧，伙计
Let's get you home, bud.
呃，你没错过多少剧情
Aw, you didn't miss much.
原来外星人抓奶牛
Turns out they were abducting cows
是为了它们的早餐麦片星球！
'cause they needed milk for their cereal planet!
爸爸，
Dad, before you go, can I ask you something?
你走之前，
before you go,
我能问你点问题吗？
can I ask you something?
好啊
Yeah, of course.
妈妈有没有跟你谈起过...
Did mom ever talk to you about...
粉钻石？
Pink Diamond?
有些事情
There were some things
你妈不那么愿意提起
your mom didn't like to talk about.
我从没有向她询问过细节
I never pressed her for details.
为什么？
Why not?
罗丝和我谈论过很多重要的事情-
Rose and I talked about tons of important stuff --
音乐，漫画，将脚伸进沙子里-
music, comic books, getting sand between your toes --
你懂的，个人感受
you know, feelings.
我们年轻时都犯过错
We both made a lot of mistakes when we were young.
我认为迪斯科会重新流行起来，她坚决反对
I thought disco was coming back, she started a war.
我认为她感觉
I think she felt like
她必须告诉我她的一切，但我告诉她，
she had to confess everything to me, but I told her,
“过去已经过去了”
"The past is the past.
“重要的是现在的你”
All that matters to me is who you are now."
而且她是一个神奇的，友爱的人
And who she was, was an incredible, loving being.
晚安，爸爸
'Night, Dad.
晚安，史蒂文
'Night, Steven.
我又回到了这里
I'm here again.
好吧，我猜我能看看周围的环境
Well, I guess I can look around.
这是哪？
What is this place?
这-这是...
What's -- what is...
Whoa!
Huh?
对不起，我待会会收拾的！
Sorry, I'll clean that up later!
当你告诉我你的梦时，
When you told me about your dream,
我就觉得耳熟
I thought it sounded familiar.
就是这个-桥子
That's it -- the Palan-kwin.
其实，这个读作“轿子”
Actually, it's pronounced "palan-keen."
是宝石人们！
It's the Gems!
他们肯定知道这是什么！
They've gotta know about this thing!
Whee! -Whoo-hoo!-Whoo！
Yo.
嘿，你知道这是什么吗？
Hey, do you know anything about this thing?
Hmm.
史蒂文，你应该知道真相，而真相是...
Steven, you deserve to know the truth, and the truth is...
我完全不知道是什么
I have no idea what that is.
我根本就没见过
I've never seen it before in my life.
让一下，紫晶，让我...
Excuse me, Amethyst. Allow me.
呃...其实...
Uh... W-well...
这看起来像是
it appears to be an illustration
某些日记中常见的幻想
in some kind of journal.
算了吧，你知道我指的是什么
Come on, you know what I mean.
我做梦梦到了这个！
I had a dream where I saw this thing!
康妮和我在想也许...
Connie and I were wondering if maybe...
史蒂文，为什么你和康妮不-
Steven, why don't you and Connie --
你们不能去！
You can't go there!
为什么不呢？
Why not?
对啊，为什么？
Yeah, why not?
我以为从此你们会告诉我所有事情
I thought you were going to tell me everything from now on.
哦，史蒂文，我们-
Oh, Steven, we--
这和粉钻有关吗？
Does this have something to do with Pink Diamond?
我已经知道妈妈打碎了她
I already know mom shattered her,
所以这个有什么不能告诉我？
so what is it about this that you can't tell me?!
停下，你让珍珠非常难受
Please, you're making Pearl very upset.
不！是我非常难受！
No! I'm very upset!
我们，不能，去
We're not going.
罗丝不想让你看到那个地方
Rose never wanted you to see this place.
罗丝想？
Rose wanted?
那我想做的呢？！
What about what I want?!
我受够了所有人都对我撒谎!
I'm sick of everyone lying to me!
罗丝是我的母亲！
Rose is my mom!
所有人里，不是我最应该知道真相吗？
Out of anyone, don't I deserve to know the truth?!
现在不行
This isn't the time.
我，不，管！我想去那里！现在！
I don't care! I want to go there now!
史蒂文！
Steven!
我对不起，我-我不应把书带来的
I'm sorry. I -- I shouldn't have brought the book.
不，你应该带来的！
Yes, you should have brought it!
还好有些东西能提供信息
It's lucky something has some information
否则我不得不她们口中撬出来！
that I don't have to get out of them!
康妮，我得带走这本书
Connie, I need to borrow this book.
可以，只是一定要小心使用
Okay, just be careful.
我一周之内还得还回图书馆呢
I gotta return it to the library in a week.
谢谢
Thanks.
等等，史蒂文，你要去-
Wait, Steven, where are you --
史蒂文，别-别走啊
Steven, don't go.
你一定要相信我
You have to trust me.
我不明白，石榴
I don't understand, Garnet.
至少你一直对我是坦诚的
At least you're usually honest with me.
我真的很想这样，
I really want to be,
但如果我告诉你为什么你不能去，
but if I tell you why you shouldn't go,
你只会心头长草的
you'll only want to go more.
啊？！那现在我更想去了！
What?! Well, now I really want to go!
我这张嘴啊～
- I shouldn't have said that.
你不能去，因为我不能跟着你
You can't go because I can't go with you!
为什么？
Why not?
石榴，为什么？
Garnet, why not?!
我...我害怕
I... I'm scared.
我-我-我不能离她太近
I-I-I can't get near her.
啊～“她”！，哪个她？
Ah, "her!" Her, who?
呃，干！
Ah, shoot!
现在草长了一米多高了
Now I've made it more interesting.
史蒂文，求求你
Steven, please!
请留下来...就当是为了我吧
Just stay here... for me.
我不会的
I won't.
我知道
I know.
- Huh?
爸爸，我需要你的帮助！
Dad, I need your help!
一切正-
Is everything o--
我在梦里看到了一个地方-而且是真实存在的-
There's this place I saw in a dream -- and it's real --
但宝石人们不愿意告诉我任何信息！
but the Gems won't tell me anything about it!
那里和粉钻石有关
It has something to do with Pink Diamond.
我知道你不想涉及到母亲的过去，
I know you didn't want to get involved with mom's past,
但我想知道真相！
but I want to know the truth!
这难道一点都不重要吗？
Doesn't that matter at all?
这当然很重要！
Of course it does!
真的？
Really?
让我看看
Let me see that.
那么宝石人不愿意带你去？
And the Gems won't take you?
是的
No.
刚好我知道个人会！
Well, I know a guy who will!
那么，宇宙一家要去韩国了
So the Universes are going to Korea.
谢谢搭我们过去，安迪叔叔！
Thank you for the ride, Uncle Andy!
啊，这不算什么
Ah, it's no problem.
俗话说，家人要帮助家人...
Like they say, family helps family...
寻找神秘的远古遗迹
find mysterious ancient artifacts.
这会非常重要
It's gonna be very serious work.
没时间闲逛
No time for fun at all.
不过，就没时间稍稍享受一下？
Well, isn't there time for a little fun?
Hmm...
谢谢！蛤？
Kamsahamnida! Huh?
干嘛这么着急？
What's the hurry?
就是这里
This is it.
你确定？
You sure this is the place?
是的，虽然很难解释，但我能感觉到
Yeah. It's hard to explain, but I can feel it.
嗯...这里还挺漂亮的
Hmm, sure is pretty here.
所以有东西让你感觉熟悉吗？
So does any of this look familiar to you?
史蒂文？喔，你还好吗？
Steven? Whoa, you okay?
你又开始流泪了！
It's happening again!
我很好，咱们接着走
I'm fine. Let's keep going.
算了，一起休息下吧
Come on, let's take a break.
我觉得这座山真的影响了你
I think this mountain's really messing you up.
不，爸爸
No, Dad.
这只可能意味着我们在接近！
This can only mean we're getting closer!
来吧！
Come on!
看！
Look!
这看起来很熟悉啊
This feels familiar.
爸爸，帮我翻过围栏
Dad, help me jump the fence.
哦，天，我们上吧
Oh, boy. We're doing this.
Oof!
喔，你老爸不能再像以前那样翻墙了
Oh, your dad really can't jump fences like he used to.
爸爸，看那个！
Dad, look!
就是这里了！
This is it!
但这个不一样啊？！
But it's different?
在我梦里，它完全损坏了，而且是粉色的
In my dream, it was all broken down and pink.
这个看起来很新
It's in perfect condition.
也许它从做了喷漆？
Maybe it got a paint job?
哦，小粉
Oh, Pink.
我对不起你，我实在对不起你
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我本来能做的更好的
I should have done more.
小黄说一切很快会结束的
Yellow says it'll all be over soon.
我在想你是怎么认为的
I wonder what you would think.
这是你的星球，毕竟
This is your planet, after all.
至少我是这么想的
I still think it is.
史蒂文，你认识她吗？
Steven, do you know her?
喔，伙计！
Whoa, buddy!
我的梦-我是从她的眼里看到的
My dreams -- I was seeing through her eyes.
我流的是她的泪！
I've been crying her tears!
你去那里做什么？
What are you doing over there?
我感觉听到了什么人
I thought I heard someone.
别急，我能搞定
Don't worry, I'll handle this.
我认为这里不止我们
I think we're not alone.
嘿！呃，今天天不错，不是吗？
Hey! Uh, nice day out, huh?
我-我没看到你，
I -- I didn't see you there.
你...呃...你好？
What's, uh... what's up?
珍珠？
Pearl?
我的钻石，我发现了个土著人
My diamond, I've found a native.
哦，呃，对！
Oh, uh, yeah!
我就来自这里！
I'm from here, all right!
“你好”，陛下
Annyeonghaseyo, your highness.
带他过来
Bring it here.
爸爸，不要！
Dad, no!
多有趣啊
How curious.
我很惊讶人类
I'm impressed by humanity's ability
在野外生存的能力
to survive in the wild.
多么奇怪的星球
What a strange planet.
还有哪里，一个脆弱如人类的存在还活着
Where else would a being as fragile as a human live,
而强大如钻石的却已消逝？
while a being as powerful as a diamond perish?
就是在这里...
This is where it happened...
她被打碎的
where she was broken.
你说完了吗？
Were you close?
很快了
Very.
噢，我非常抱歉
Oh, I'm awfully sorry.
我能理解想继续生活有多难
I know how hard it is to move on
当你失去你关心的人时
when you've lost someone.
真的？
You do?
我也失去了一个对我非常重要的人
I lost someone very important to me, too.
我每天都在思念她
I miss her every single day,
每时每刻都是
and I think about her all the time.
但，她并不会回来了
But she's never coming back.
这种感觉很难承受
That feeling can be so hard to be okay with.
我很惊讶一个人类
I'm surprised that a human being
能理解我的感受
is capable of understanding how I feel.
真是羞愧啊
It's a shame.
你的星球孕育着一个致命武器
There's a geo-weapon incubating in your planet
它将很快摧毁一切
that will destroy everything shortly.
但，你不应承受这些，不是吗？
But you don't deserve that, do you?
致命武器，对吧？
Geo-weapon, huh?
你知道，我真的不应该出现在车里
You know, I really shouldn't be here,
但我很高兴我来了，最，后，一，次
but I'm glad I came back one last time.
我可以最后再挽救她一次遗产
I can save one last piece of her legacy.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah? Oof!
爸爸！
Dad!
那真是个巨大的胳膊啊！
That's a big arm!
把我放下来，求求你了！
Put me down, please!
哦！喔！
Oh, whoa!
将我放下吧，陛下！
Put me down, your highness!
Whoa! Whoa!
爸爸，爸爸！
Dad, Dad!
停下！
Stop!
爸爸...
Dad.
史蒂文，我-我对不起！
Steven, I'm -- I'm sorry!
石榴！
Garnet!
我“看到”你来了这里
I saw you come here.
我“看到”蓝钻石在地球上
I saw Blue Diamond on Earth.
我“看到”她见到我并找到了我们所有人
I saw her see me and find all of us.
我不能和你出现在这里
I couldn't be here with you.
她抓走了我爸爸！
She took my dad!
这都是我的错，我本该听你的话的！
It's all my fault. - I should have listened to you!
我们该怎么办，石榴？
What are we gonna do, Garnet?
我们要前往深空，我们要将他救回来
We're going to space. We're going to get him back.